{
    "classes": [
        "ORG",
        "PERSON",
        "GPE",
        "LOC",
        "VEHICLE"
    ],
    "annotations": [
        [
            "AMERICAN AIRLINES,US AIRWAYS,AIRCRAFT N953UW,EMBRAER E190 SUFFERED DMG WHILST LANDING,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        17,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        18,
                        28,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        38,
                        44,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "AMERICAN AIRLINES, Aircraft Boeing 787 Regn N805AN suffered damage due to hail, Beijing, China",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        17,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        28,
                        50,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        80,
                        94,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "AMERICAN AIRLINES, USAirways-250515, Damage to aircraft Airbus A320 N668AW due to hard landing ",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        17,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        56,
                        74,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "AMERICAN AIRLINES,AIRCRAFT N917AN, 1999 B737-800,SUFFERED DMG DUE TO TAIL STRIKE,LAGUARDIA,NEW YORK.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        17,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        27,
                        33,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        81,
                        99,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "AMERICAN AIRLINES,FOD TO ENGINE DUE TO INGESTION OF BIRDS,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        17,
                        "ORG"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "AMERICAN AIRLINES,AIRCRAFT N768AN,BOEING 777 SUFFERED DMG WHILE AWAITING CLEARANCE TO TAKE-OFF,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        17,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        27,
                        33,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "MALAYSIAN AIRLINE SYSTEM BERHAD, Aircarft B737-800, Reg 9M-MLT was hit by Miascor lavatory truck, MANILA",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        31,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        42,
                        50,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        98,
                        104,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "VIETNAM AIRLINES CORPORATION,AIRCRAFT A321-VNA608 HAD TAIL STRIKE DURING TAKE OFF,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        28,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        38,
                        49,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "VIETNAM AIRLINES CORP,LOSS OF SAMSUNG SHIPMENT,NOI BAI,VIETNAMTO ROISSY,CHARLES DE GAULLE,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        21,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        47,
                        54,
                        "LOC"
                    ],
                    [
                        72,
                        89,
                        "PERSON"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "DASSAULT FLACON 7X. HZ-SPAI,TRENT ENGINE S/N 41853 DMG TO MAIN GEAR BOX AND OIL SYSTEM,JEDDAH.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        87,
                        93,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "SAUDI ARABIAN AIRLINES CORP,SAUDIA AIRCRAFT B-747 (HZ-A14) DMGD DURING MAINTENANCE TO HANGAR,JEDDAH.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        27,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        28,
                        58,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        93,
                        99,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "SAUDI ARABIAN AIRLINES CORP,DMG TO FORWARD FLANGE OF FAN CASE GENX ENGINE S/N 959153,BRAZIL,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        27,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        85,
                        91,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "EMIRATES GROUP,AINS-0292,DMG TO LH T/R DUCK (4 QUANTITY),",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        14,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        15,
                        24,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "CATHAY PACIFIC AIRWAYS LTD,INJURY TO LUK FUNG YEE,SINGAPORE TO HONG KONG.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        26,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        37,
                        49,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        50,
                        59,
                        "GPE"
                    ],
                    [
                        63,
                        72,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "CATHAY PACIFIC AIRWAYS LTD,DIVERSION OF FLIGHT CX884 DUE TO SMOKE IN THE CABIN,HONG KONG-LOS ANGELES,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        1,
                        25,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        47,
                        52,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        79,
                        88,
                        "GPE"
                    ],
                    [
                        89,
                        100,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "FIN GROUP,JET2 2014/15 LIABILITY FUND FILE HELD BY CLYDE & CO.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        9,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        51,
                        61,
                        "ORG"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "AMERICAN AIRLINES, LIABILITY FUND FOR LOSSES OCCURING BETWEEN 22ND DEC 2014 TO 22 DEC 2015",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        17,
                        "ORG"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "AMERICAN AIRLINES,PASSENGER SONYA DOCKETT,STRUCK BY LIGHTNING WHILE WALKING FROM TARMAC TO TERMINAL BUILDING,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        17,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        28,
                        41,
                        "PERSON"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "AMERICAN AIRLINES,US AIRWAYS,PLAINTIFFS ALG INFANT WAS BURNED DURING FLIGHT 754,IN FLIGHT.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        17,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        18,
                        28,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        69,
                        79,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "AMERICAN AIRLINES,PLAINTIFF ALLEGING RIGHT FEMUR FRACTURE,TOTAL RIGHT KNEE REPLACEMENT,HAIRLINE FRACTURE TO TIBIA,WOUNDS/ULCERS FROM CAST & DISLOCATED ANKLE ,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        17,
                        "ORG"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "CATHAY PACIFIC AIRWAYS LTD,DIVERSION OF FLIGHT CX884 DUE TO SMOKE IN THE CABIN,HONG KONG-LOS ANGELES,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        26,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        47,
                        52,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        79,
                        88,
                        "GPE"
                    ],
                    [
                        89,
                        100,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "KUWAIT AIRWAYS CORP,FLIGHT NO KU087,CARRYING MEDICAL DONATIONS CARGO,ON ARRIVAL FLIGHT PACK CONSISTING OF 139 ITEMS & TOOLS TO BE MISSING,KUWAIT.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        19,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        30,
                        35,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        138,
                        144,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "ETHIOPIAN A/L ENTERPRISE,WHILST LANDING IT VEERED OFF RUNWAY RESULTING IN NOSE WHEEL BEING SEVERED,GHANA.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        24,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        99,
                        104,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "CIVIL AVIATION ADMINISTRATION OF CHINA,DAMAGE TO YIFENG JET BOMBARDIER CL605,SHENZHEN AIRPORT.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        38,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        49,
                        76,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        77,
                        93,
                        "LOC"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "CIVIL AVIATION ADMINISTRATION OF CHINA,AIRBUS A330 REGN B-5935 REPORTED DMG IN GROUND,GUIYANG AIRPORT.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        38,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        39,
                        62,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        86,
                        101,
                        "LOC"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "CIVIL AVIATION ADMINISTRATION OF CHINA,CHINA SOUTHERN AIRLINES CZ6002 & CHINA EASTERN AIRLINES MU2491 COLLIDED,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        38,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        39,
                        62,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        63,
                        69,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        72,
                        94,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        95,
                        101,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "CIVIL AVIATION ADMINISTRATION OF CHINA,CHINA SOUTHERN AIRLINES CZ6002 & CHINA EASTERN AIRLINES MU2491 COLLIDED,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        38,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        39,
                        62,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        63,
                        69,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        72,
                        94,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        95,
                        101,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "CIVIL AVIATION ADMINISTRATION OF CHINA,HAINAN AIRLINES,A330/B-5935 WERE REPORTED DMG IN GROUND INCIDENT,GUIYANG (LONGDONGBAO),",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        38,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        39,
                        54,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        55,
                        66,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        104,
                        124,
                        "LOC"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "ABM INDUSTRIES,AIR SERV CORP,US NON MEDICARE BLOCK FILE.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        14,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        15,
                        28,
                        "ORG"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "BEIJING CAPITAL INTL,BOEING 787-8,REGN:B2768 DGED BY AIRBRIDGE,BEIJING.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        20,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        39,
                        44,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        53,
                        62,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        63,
                        70,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "BEIJING CAPITAL INTL AIRPORT GRP CO,THIRD PARTY EMIRATES HAINAN AIRLINES A300-200/B-6519 DMGD,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        35,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        48,
                        56,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        57,
                        72,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        73,
                        88,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "PORT AUTHORITY OF NEW YORK AND NEW JERSEY,CLMNT KENIA CABRERA SUSTAINED AS A RESULT OF MOTOR VEHICLE ACCIDENT WITH SALT & SAND,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        41,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        48,
                        61,
                        "PERSON"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "HAECO,TRAFFIC ACCIDENT INVOLVING VEHICLE NO. PC78 (HAE-00500) & HAS's STR.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        5,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        45,
                        49,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        51,
                        60,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "TAECO, THIRD PARTY CATHAY PACIFIC B777-200,REG B-HNC DMGE TO MAIN LANDING GEAR, TAECO XIAMEN",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        5,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        19,
                        33,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        34,
                        42,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        80,
                        85,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        86,
                        92,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "TAECO,WIDESPREAD PITTING CORROSION DAMAGE TO AIRCRAFT JA8887 AFTER PAINT REMOVAL,SHANDONG.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        5,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        54,
                        60,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        81,
                        89,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "TAECO, THIRD PARTY CATHAY PACIFIC REGN.B-HNA - NO.1 ENGINE SUSTAINED HEAT DAMAGE.NAGOYA, JAPAN",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        5,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        19,
                        33,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        81,
                        94,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "FRONTIER FLYING SERVICE INC,PIPER NAVAJO,CLMNT ALICE SWAN SLIPPED & FELL FROM AIR STAIR,KOTZEBUE,AK.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        27,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        28,
                        40,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        47,
                        57,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        88,
                        100,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "LINEA AEREA AMASZONAS, CAPTAIN ALVAREZ SUFFERED INJURY AND RELATED MEDICAL EXPENSES FOLLOWING AN IN FLIGHT BIRDSTRIKE, BOLIVIA",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        21,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        23,
                        38,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        119,
                        126,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "LINEA AEREA AMASZONAS, CAPTAIN ALVAREZ SUFFERED INJURY AND RELATED MEDICAL EXPENSES FOLLOWING AN IN FLIGHT BIRDSTRIKE, BOLIVIA",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        21,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        23,
                        38,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        119,
                        126,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "BRISTOW GROUP,SIKORSKT-92, REGN; G-CIGZ, SUSTAINED DMG TO CT7 ENGINE,ABERDEEN,SCOTLAND.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        13,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        14,
                        25,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        69,
                        86,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "TEXTRON INC,BEECHCRAFT KING AIR 200 CRASH INTO BUILDING AFTER TAKE OFF,WICHITA MID CONTINENT AIRPORT.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        11,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        12,
                        35,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        71,
                        100,
                        "LOC"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "THE BOEING CO,AIR ALGERIE MD 83 EC LTV DMG,GOSSI MALI.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        13,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        14,
                        25,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        26,
                        34,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        43,
                        53,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "BOEING CO,JAMCO EMPLOYEE FATALLY INJD WHILST REPLACING SEATBELT AIRBAG ASSEMBLY IN FIRST CLASS CABIN,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        9,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        10,
                        15,
                        "ORG"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "BOEING CO,DMG TO ASIANA AIRLINES A320-232 DUE TO CRASH LANDING,HIROSHIMA AIRPORT,JAPAN.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        9,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        17,
                        32,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        33,
                        41,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        63,
                        87,
                        "LOC"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "CURTISS WRIGHT CORP,AN APACHE AH-64D HELICOPTER OPERATED BY DUTCH MILITARY CRASHED IN MALI,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        19,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        23,
                        29,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        30,
                        47,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        60,
                        74,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        86,
                        90,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "BOEING CO,SOUTHWEST AIRLINES B737-800 REG.N8647A EXPERIENCED CABIN DECOMPRESSURIZATION,HAD TO MAKE EMERGENCY LANDING,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        9,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        10,
                        28,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        29,
                        37,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "BOEING CO,U.S.M.C MV-22B CRASHED DURING LANDING,OAHU,HAWAII.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        9,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        10,
                        17,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        18,
                        24,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        48,
                        59,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "BOEING CO,AMERICAN AIRLINES FLIGHT 953 SUDDEN DROP FO APPROX 3,000 FEET MID FLIGHT,VARS PASSENGERS & CREW INJURED,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        9,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        10,
                        27,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        28,
                        38,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "LEFIELL MANUFACTURING CO,ALGD SUPPLY OF A DEFECTIVE F117 LOW PRESSURE TURBINE SHAFT TO UTC,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        24,
                        "ORG"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "MECAER AVIATION GROUP, AW139 REGISTRATION MARK N1NJ SUFFERED DMGS TO THE TAIL BOOM, ROTOR AND SERVO INPUT LEVER, NORTHEAST PHILADELPHIA AIRPORT",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        21,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        113,
                        143,
                        "ORG"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "MECAER AVIATION GRP,AIRCRAFT EA 500 SUFFERED COLLAPSED LEFT LANDING GEAR WHILE TAXING,SACRAMENTO EXECUTIVE AIRPORT,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        19,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        29,
                        35,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        86,
                        114,
                        "ORG"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "TEXTRON INC,BEECHCRAFT KING AIR 200 CRASH INTO BUILDING AFTER TAKE OFF,WICHITA MID CONTINENT AIRPORT.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        11,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        12,
                        35,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        71,
                        100,
                        "ORG"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "TRANSDIGM GROUP INC, WRONGFUL DEATH CLAIM OF GREEN BERET CAPTAIN JAMES AHN WHEN HIS MC-4 PARACHUTE MALFUNCTIONED DURING, SHELTON WA",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        19,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        121,
                        131,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "TRANSDIGM GROUP INC,CODY GIBSON,CATASTROPHICALLY INJURED WHEN HIS T-11 PARACHUTE SYSTEM FAILED TO OPEN,FORT BRAGG,NORTH CAROLINA.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        19,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        20,
                        31,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        103,
                        128,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "TRANSDIGM GROUP INC, PRODUCTS LIABILITY ACTION FOR WRONGFUL DEATH FOLLOWING PLANE CRASH, EL CAJON CA",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        19,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        89,
                        100,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "TRANSDIGM GROUP INC,VEHICLE COLLISION,CHICAGO,ILLINOIS.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        19,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        38,
                        54,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "TRANSDIGM GROUP INC,ESTATE OF PHIL JAMES DRYDEN CRASH OF CESSNA 182T AIRCRAFT N784CP,MOBILE REGIONAL AIRPORT IN ALABAMA. ",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        19,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        30,
                        40,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        78,
                        84,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        85,
                        119,
                        "ORG"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "PRECISION AIRCRAFT SOLUTIONS,LLC,DAVID LAMBERT,CLMNT HIRED BY AERO AIR LLC TO WORK ON CARGO DOOR ASSEMBLY PROJECT WHEN HE FELL FROM PLATFORM,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        28,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        33,
                        46,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        62,
                        74,
                        "ORG"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "GENCORP,AEROJET ROCKETDYNE,VERTICAL PLAN,USA.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        7,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        8,
                        26,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        27,
                        40,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        41,
                        44,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "SABRELINER AVIATION LLC,DAWN BAKER LAWSUIT,FLIGHT BREAK UP & CRASH OF A CESSNA 525 OPERATED BY DONALD BAKER,CRASH RESULTED IN DEATH OF DAWN BAKER,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        23,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        95,
                        107,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        135,
                        145,
                        "PERSON"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "SABRELINER AVIATION LLC,COMPLAINT SERVED AGAINST SIERRA INDUSTRIES & INNOVA AEROPSACE FOR DMGS ARISING FROM BREACH OF CONTRACT.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        19,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        49,
                        85,
                        "ORG"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "TAILWIND TECHNOLOGIES,TAILWIND HARTZELL,RAYTHEON KINGAIR B200,N52SZ SUFFERED POWER LOSS ON TAKEOFF,USA.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        21,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        22,
                        39,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        40,
                        61,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        62,
                        67,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        99,
                        103,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "ROLLS ROYCE PLC,ACCIDENT INVOLVING A400M (MSN023) IN SEVILLE.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        15,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        42,
                        48,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        50,
                        60,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "ROLLS ROYCE PLC,BELL 206L CRASHED WHILST BEING USED FOR CONTROLLED FOREST BURNING,MISSISSIPPI,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        15,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        16,
                        25,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        82,
                        93,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "ROLLS ROYCE, ENGINE FAILURE LED TO HARD LANDING, CRESCO, IOWA",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        11,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        49,
                        61,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Various Losses Block Entry",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ],
        [
            "GENERAL ELECTRIC CO,BRITISH AIRWAYS FLIGHT 2276 EXPERIENCED 1 ENGINE FAILURE DURING TAKEOFF,LAS VEGAS.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        19,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        20,
                        47,
                        "VEHICLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        92,
                        101,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "GENERAL ELECTRIC CO,MAGNESTOS WAS SUBSTANTIALLY DMGD AFTER FORCED LANDING IN STEPHENVILLE,TEXAS.",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        19,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        77,
                        95,
                        "GPE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "GENERAL ELECTRIC CO,TECHNOAVIA SMG-92 (JA-YDJ) EQUIPPED WITH A WALTER M601D ENGINE LOST POWER SHORTLY AFTER TAKE-OFF,",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        19,
                        "ORG"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ],
        [
            "Default Event for LimClm Created Claims",
            {
                "entities": []
            }
        ]
    ]
}